所以我们要一起行动我们要
So we're gonna do an exercise together,
we're going to,
也要让猫在这个特定的情况下工作，对吧 ?
Make cat work in this particular
scenario as well, right?
我要你做的就是你要输入 " 我的秘密汽水配方"
So what I'm gonna have you do is you're
gonna type, echo "my secret soda recipe"
像那样的文秘
into secret.txt like that.
在这里，你可以看到我有一个 secreta.txt，对吧 ?
Here, you can see that I have
a secret.txt, right there, right?
所以现在我要说的是什么颜色的
So now if I say, chroot.tash like that,
这一下降很快就会进入我的 Linux 监狱了对吧
this drop soon into my Linux
jailed process, right?
如果我输入的类型是我可以看到的，如果我输入 pwd ，你可以看到
If I type ls I can see this and
if I type pwd, you can see
我在这个根目录下，看不到它，对吧 ?
that I'm in this root directory,
can't see outside of it, right?.
现在，如果我输入 cat secret.txt，那么找不到命令，对吗 ?
Now if I type cat secret.txt,
command not found, right?
因为猫不在这儿所以这是你的任务
Because cat is not in here, so
that's your assignment for this exercise.